authintmail.com 2014-03-13

# Privacy Policy | Authint Mail

Last updated 10 February 2014 - 8:44am GMT

This Privacy Policy discloses the privacy practices for Authint Mail News Portal Web site and other applications (collectively referred to as the “AM Services”), and to any services that display this notice. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to "Authint Mail" include authintmail.com.

* * *

 **WHAT INFORMATION DO WE GATHER ABOUT YOU?**

The information Authint Mail gathers falls into two categories: 

  1. Personal information, which includes personal information you supply when you subscribe, order, complete a survey, register for our site, enter a contest or provide your e-mail address and 
  2. Non-personal information collected through technology, which includes tracking information collected as you use the AM Services.

* * *

 **Personal Information That You Give Us**

 **Registration Information**

Registration for the AM Services may require that you supply certain personal information, including a unique e-mail address and demographic information to register.

 **User Generated Content and Public Activities (Including Comments & Reader Reviews)**

We offer you opportunities to engage in public activities on authintmail.com and other AM Services. "Public activities" are any actions you take on authintmail.com that are designed to be visible to other users, including comments, recommendations, blurbs, ratings or any other items that you submit. Any information you disclose in your public activities, along with your screen name or ID, or any image or photo, becomes public and may be used by The Authint Mail for online and offline promotional or commercial uses in any and all media. If you choose to engage in public activities, you should be aware that any personal information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these areas, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums and The Authint Mail has no responsibility to publish, take down, remove or edit any of your public activities or any of your submissions that are a result of your public activities.

When you share or recommend (with or without adding your own comments) any authintmail.com articles or content to your Facebook, Twitter or other social networking profile, that action is governed by their respective Privacy Policy. We do not track or store a record of those comments or actions.

If you have registered for an authintmail.com account, we will track and aggregate your public activities on authintmail.com. By choosing to participate in public activities, you are electing to share and display such public activities via authintmail.com. Also, public activities may be included in RSS feeds, APIs and made available to other Web sites via other formats. As a result, your public activities may appear on other Web sites, blogs, or feeds. Keep in mind that we are not responsible for any personal information you choose to make public via your public activities, and you agree that such sharing will be deemed to have been done by you, not The Authint Mail. 

 **Contests, Sweepstakes and Special Offers**

The Authint Mail collects personal information from you in connection with optional sweepstakes, contests or special offers. If this information is also being collected by a third party other than Authint Mail, we will notify you at the same time. If you do not want any personal information shared, you may always decline to participate in the sweepstakes, contest or special offer.

* * *

 **Non-Personal Information Collected Using Technology**

We use various Internet technologies to manage the AM Services and track use of the Services. Non-personal information that we collect using these technologies may be combined with other information about you.

 **Device Information**

We may collect non-personal information about the computer, mobile device or other device you use to access the AM Services, such as IP address, geolocation information, unique device identifiers, browser type, browser language and other transactional information.

 **Cookies, Beacons, Local Storage and Other Similar Technologies**

In providing the AM Services, we use "cookies," Web beacons, HTML5 local storage and other similar technologies to manage access to and use of the Services, recognize you and provide personalization, as well as to help us understand where our visitors are going and how much time they spend there. You will not be able to access certain areas of authintmail.com website, if your computer does not accept cookies from us. For more detailed information about our use of cookies read our **[Cookie Policy](https://www.authintmail.com/legal/cookies)**.

 **Analytics Technologies**

We have hired third parties to provide us information, reports and analysis about the usage, browsing patterns of users of the AM Services. 

Google Analytics tracks and analyzes non-personally identifiable usage and volume statistical information from our visitors and customers on authintmail.com. All data collected by Google Analytics on our behalf is owned and used by us. For more information about how Google Analytics collects data, please read their privacy policy at **[Google Analytics Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html)**.

 **IP Addresses**

Authint Mail logs Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, or the location of your computer on the Internet, for systems administration and troubleshooting purposes. We use this information in an aggregate fashion to track access to our Web sites and mobile applications.

 **Log Files and Your Reading History**

We automatically log certain usage information about your use of AM Service. This information includes a reading history of the pages you view. We use these log files to analyse usage of our Web sites and mobile applications.

 **Disqus Commenting system**

Authint Mail used Disqus commenting system to collect user opinion and feedback, you can read about disqus's privacy polict at **[Privacy Policy](http://help.disqus.com/customer/portal/articles/466259-privacy-policy). **To know more about Disqus please read their **[About](http://disqus.com/about/)** and [**Terms**](http://docs.disqus.com/kb/terms-and-policies) page

 **Cloudflare System**

We use cloudflare systems to protect our data and services, you can read about the by visiting **[CloudFlare privacy& security policy](https://www.cloudflare.com/security-policy)**

* * *

 **WHAT DO WE DO WITH THE INFORMATION WE GATHER ABOUT YOU?**

 **Providing the Services You Request**

We use the information we gather about you to enable your use of the AM Services, fulfill your requests for certain products and services, such as enabling you to participate in AM services, polls, contests, and message boards.

 **Statistical Analysis**

We perform statistical, demographic and marketing analyses of users of the AM Services, and their subscribing and purchasing patterns, for product development purposes and to generally inform advertisers about the nature of our subscriber base. We use this information for analysis purposes, including analysis to improve customer relationships.

 **Customizing Your Experience**

We use the information that we collect to allow advertising to be targeted to the users for whom such advertising is most pertinent. We also use this information to customize certain features of the AM Services to provide you with an enhanced experienced based on the type of device you are using to access AM Services, and in certain cases, provide you with requested services.

 **Relevant Advertising**

We may use demographic and preference information to allow advertising on the AM Service to be targeted to the users for whom they are most pertinent. This means users see advertising that is most likely to interest them, and advertisers send their messages to people who are most likely to be receptive, improving both the viewer's experience and the effectiveness of the ads. We disclose information to third parties only in aggregate or de-identified form.

* * *

 **IS MY INFORMATION PROTECTED?**

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy and ensure the appropriate use of information, we have put in place commercially reasonable physical, technical and administrative controls to protect the information. Please note that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure.

* * *

 **Compliance With Legal Process**

We may disclose personal information if we are required to do so by law or we have a good faith belief that such action is necessary to

  1. comply with the law or with legal process;
  2. protect and defend our rights and property;
  3. protect against misuse or unauthorized use of the AM Services; or
  4. protect the personal safety or property of our users or the public (among other things, this means that if you provide false information or attempt to pose as someone else, information about you may be disclosed as part of any investigation into your actions).

 **COPPA Compliance**

Authint Mail or it's associated services does not knowingly collect or store any personal information about children under the age of thirteen (13).

* * *

 **Changes to This Policy**

This Privacy Policy may be amended from time to time. Any such changes will be posted on this page. If we make a significant or material change in the way we use your personal information, the change will be posted on this page thirty (30) days prior to taking effect and registered users will be notified via e-mail.

If you have any concerns or would like to know  more, please feel free to contact us at **[Support](https://www.authintmail.com/form/contact-us)**
